### PERSONAL INFORMATION

# Sujata Sule

- Olkipolku 5, 02620 Espoo (Finland)
- **(+358)458649559**
- xujata.p.sule@gmail.com
- in https://www.linkedin.com/in/sujata-sule-84080727/

Sex Female | Date of birth 29 Dec 1979 | Nationality Finnish

#### PERSONAL STATEMENT

A qualified and enthusiastic professional, with over 6 years' worth of experience, currently searching for an internship in the field of software testing as a part of my recent study to utilize my skills and take the next step in my career.

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

### 1 Jun 2016-31 Dec 2016

### Software tester

EarthCape Oy, Helsinki (Finland)

- -Done manual testing
- -Wrote test cases for the application

### 1 Jul 2004-Apr 2010

### **Business lecturer**

RTM Nagpur University, Nagpur (India)

- -Taught subjects like Marketing Management, Business Economics, Human Skills, and Environment Management.
- -Academic administration was a part of my job
- -Organized guest lecture activity
- -Event Manager for college events.
- -Assisted placements of the college.
- -Promoted various study programs of university in Expo 2006.

## **EDUCATION AND TRAINING**

### 7 Jan 2019-Present

## Full Stack Web Development Program

Helsinki Business College, Helsinki (Finland)

- -HTML
- -CSS
- -JavaScript
- -React JS
- -Node JS
- -Data Structure
- -UI Design
- -Quality Assurance



### 10 Jan 2011-30 Nov 2011

# Finnish Language Course

TE-Office, Espoo (Finland)

## 1 Aug 2001-31 May 2003

# Master of Business Administration(MBA)

Nagpur University, Nagpur (India)

General

- -Business Economics
- -Management Accounting
- -Business Ethics
- -Entrepreneurship Development
- -Corporate Law
- -Human Resource Management
- -Financial Management
- -Management to Information Technology

Specialization

-Marketing Management

### 1 Jul 2004-31 May 2008

## Master of Commerce

Nagpur University, Nagpur (India)

General

- -Organisation of commerce
- -Financial Accounting
- -Corporate Law
- -Business Economics

Specialization

-International Marketing

## 1 Jul 1998-May 2001

# **Bachelor of Commerce**

Nagpur University, Nagpur (India)

General

- -English
- -International Economics
- -Accounting
- -Secretarial Practice
- -Mercantile Law

## PERSONAL SKILLS

Mother tongue(s)

Marathi, Hindi

# Foreign language(s)

UNDERSTANDING		SPEAKING		WRITING
Listening	Reading	Spoken interaction	Spoken production	
B2	B2	B2	B2	B2
		IELTS-6.5		

English



Curriculum vitae Sujata Sule

Finnish

A2 A2 A1 A1 A2

YKI caertificate

Levels: A1 and A2: Basic user - B1 and B2: Independent user - C1 and C2: Proficient user

Common European Framework of Reference for Languages

#### Communication skills

- -good communication skill aguired as a lecturer
- -good in interaction with team due to volunteer work

### Organisational / managerial skills

- -oragnizational skills gained through my work experience as an event manager for college events
- -organizing many events for Non-profit-association called IWF ry, Finland

#### Job-related skills

- -independent user of MS excel
- good understanding of software development process
- -good in writing test cases
- 2 months training in software testing, developed skills required for quality assurance.
- -basic knowledge of automation tools
- -knowledge of defect life cycle
- -defect reporting

## Digital skills

SELF-ASSESSMENT						
Information processing	Communication	Content creation	Safety	Problem- solving		
Independent user	Proficient user	Independent user	Basic user	Basic user		

Digital skills - Self-assessment grid

Full Stack Web Developer Program, Helsinki Business College.

2 months Software testing training.

**Driving licence** 

A. B

## ADDITIONAL INFORMATION

## Memberships

Position of trust: Board member in IWF ry from 2016

I am working as a board member for the non-profit association called Indian Women in Finland(IWF ry). This volunteer work is developing and refreshing my skills like communication, organization and administration.